Inventory of the Benjamin Stoddert Ewell Papers 1784-1934
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Letters, 1784-1934. (Folder 1-19)
  - Letters: E, 1784-1934 (Folder 3-10)
    - Letters from Elizabeth S. Ewell, sister of Benjamin S. Ewell, May 1834-July 1894., 40 items. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.) to Rebecca L. Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia. Postmarked Georgetown, D.C., 31 May 1839. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.) to Benjamin S. Ewell, at Prince Edward Court House, Virginia. Postmarked Buckland, June 1842-August 1844., 3 items. (Folder 8)
        - Letter, June 1842. (Folder 8)
        - Letter, 13 January 1844. (Folder 8)
        - Letter, 17 August 1844. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.) to her mother, Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia. Postmarked Washington, D.C., 19 October 1844. (Folder 8)
        This letter is readdressed to Professor Ewell, Prince Edward County, Virginia, with a postscript by Elizabeth Ewell.
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, D.C., to Benjamin S. Ewell, at Prince Edward Court House, Virginia, 11 March 1845. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Upper Marlboro, Maryland, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at Prince Edward Court House, Virginia, 15 January 1846. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, D.C., to Benjamin S. Ewell, 6 November 1850. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, D.C., to William Stoddert, 8 December 1850. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, D.C., to Rebecca L. Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia, 19 February 1851. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, D.C., to Benjamin S. Ewell, March 1851. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, D.C., to Rebecca L. Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia, 9 May 1852. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, to Rebecca L. Ewell, 11 June 1852. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, to Rebecca L. Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia, 30 August 1852. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, to Rebecca L. Ewell, March 1855-October 1858., 3 items. (Folder 8)
        - Letter, 18 March 1855. (Folder 8)
        - Letter, 24 August 1857. (Folder 8)
        - Letter, 3 October 1858. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, to her niece, Elizabeth S. Ewell, daughter of Benjamin S. Ewell, 23 April 1865. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.) to Benjamin S. Ewell, August 1875-September 1876., 2 items. (Folder 8)
        - Letter, 17 August 1875. (Folder 8)
        - Letter, 14 September 1876. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, D.C., to Benjamin S. Ewell, April 1884-May 1885., 2 items. (Folder 8)
        - Letter, 2 April 1884. (Folder 8)
        - Letter, 5 May 1885. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, D.C., to Benjamin S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia, 19 January 1887. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, D.C., to Benjamin S. Ewell, 22 December 1887. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, D.C., to Benjamin S. Ewell, at Ewell's, James City County, Virginia, 20 December 1888. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, D.C., to her niece, Elizabeth Ewell Scott, June-July 1894., 2 items. (Folder 8)
        - Letter, 21 June 1894. (Folder 8)
        - Letter, 16 July 1894. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, to Benjamin S. Ewell. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Stony Lonesome, Prince William County, Virginia, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at Prince Edward Court House, Virginia. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Upper Marlboro, Maryland, to Benjamin S. Ewell. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.) to her mother, Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia Postmarked Georgetown, D.C.. (Folder 8)
        Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell to Benjamin S. Ewell. (On same sheet.)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, to her niece, Elizabeth S. Ewell, daughter of Benjamin S. Ewell, undated., Two undated letters. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, D.C., to Rebecca Ewell. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Georgetown, to Rebecca L. Ewell, at Bristow Station, Prince William County, Virginia. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.) to Rebecca L. Ewell, at Bladensburgh, Prince George's County, Maryland. Postmarked Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.) to Rebecca L. Ewell, Virginia. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.) to Rebecca L. Ewell., Three letters. (Folder 8)
    - Letters from Elizabeth S. Ewell, daughter of Benjamin S. Ewell. February 1847-August 1867., 6 items. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth) to her father, Benjamin S. Ewell, 9 February 1847. (Folder 8)
        Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell to her son, Benjamin S. Ewell. (On same sheet.)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth), at Williamsburg, Virginia, to her aunt, Rebecca Ewell, 23 August 1867. (Folder 8)
        Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell to Rebecca Ewell. (On same sheet.)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth), at College Hill, to her father, B. S. Ewell, no date. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth) to B. S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia. Postmarked Buckland, no date. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth S.), at Williamsburg, Virginia, to her aunt, Rebecca Ewell, no date. (Folder 8)
      - Ewell (Elizabeth), at the University of Virginia, to Bessie Hoge, no date. (Folder 8)
    - Ewell (Mr. & Mrs. J. B.), at Waco, Texas, to Mrs. And Mrs. B. S. Scott, no date. (Folder 9)
      An invitation to the marriage ceremony of their daughter.
    - Ewell (Jesse), grandfather of Benjamin S. Ewell, at Bel Air, Prince William County, Virginia, to his son, Thomas Ewell, December 1800-April 1802., 3 items. (Folder 9)
      - Letter, 8 December 1800. (Folder 9)
      - Letter, 17 [ ? ] 1801. (Folder 9)
      - Letter, 16 April 1802. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Jesse), at Dumfries, Prince William County, Virginia, to Thomas Ewell, at GeorgeTown, District of Columbia, 10 January 1803. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Jesse), at Bel Air, Prince William County, Virginia, to Thomas Ewell, at George Town, District of Columbia, April-May 1803., 2 items. (Folder 9)
      - Letter, 8 April 1803. (Folder 9)
      - Letter, 22 May 1803. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Jesse), at Dumfries, to Alfred [ ? ], 3 September 1803. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Jesse), at Bel Air, Prince William County, Virginia, to his son, Thomas Ewell, Ca. 1804. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Jesse), at Dumfries, to Thomas Ewell, at George-town, D.C., 1 August 180[?]. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Jesse) to Thomas Ewell, at George Town, District of Columbia. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Jesse), at Bel Air, to Thomas Ewell. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Jesse), at Ruckersville, Green County, Virginia, to Bessie Scott Crawford, at Williamsburg, Virginia, 9 January 1914. (Folder 9)
      Enclosure: Post card from Susan Hutchison, at Manassas, Prince William County, Virginia, to Jesse Ewell, at Ruckersville, Virginia, 8 January 1913. Postmarked 1914.
    - Ewell (Jesse), at Ruckersville, Virginia, to Bessie Scott Crawford, 30 January 1914. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Jesse, Jr.), at Ruckersville, Greene County, Virginia, to Col. Benjamin S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia, 24 March 1886. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Jesse, Sr.), at Hickory Grove P.O., Prince William County, Virginia, to Elizabeth S. Ewell, sister of Benjamin S. Ewell, September-October 1880., 2 items. (Folder 9)
      - Letter, 30 September 1880. (Folder 9)
      - Letter, 21 October 1880. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (John S.) Hickory Grove, Virginia, to Benjamin S. Ewell, 15 March 1893. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Julia), i.e., Mrs. Benjamin S. Ewell, to Rebecca L. Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia. Postmarked York, Pennsylvania, 11 May 1850. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Lizinka Campbell), at St. Louis, to her niece, Elizabeth Ewell, daughter of Benjamin S. Ewell, 4 April 1865. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Lizinka Campbell), at Springhill, Tennessee, to Elizabeth Ewell, 25 April 1866. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Lizinka Campbell), at Springhill, Tennessee, to Elizabeth Ewell, 22 February 1867. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Lizinka Campbell), at Springhill, Tennessee, to Benjamin S. Ewell, July-August 1867., 2 items. (Folder 9)
      - Letter, 16 July 1867. (Folder 9)
      - Letter, 26 August 1867. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Lizinka Campbell) to Elizabeth Ewell, no date. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Paul H.), at Centreville, Fairfax County, Virginia, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at West Point, New York, 10 May 1829. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Paul H.), to Benjamin S. Ewell, at West Point, New York. Postmarked Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia, 14 February 1831. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.) to Benjamin Stoddert Ewell, at West Point, New York. Postmarked Hay Market, Prince William County, Virginia, 15 March 1831. (Folder 9)
      Postscript by Elizabeth Ewell.
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.) to B. S. Ewell, at West Point, New York. Postmarked Bladensburg, Maryland, 15 May 1835. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.) to Benjamin S. Ewell, at York, Pennsylvania. Postmarked Haymarket, Virginia, November 1836. (Folder 9)
      Postscript by Elizabeth S. Ewell.
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.) to Benjamin S. Ewell, at York, Pennsylvania. Postmarked Bladensburg, Maryland, May 1838. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.), at Stony Lonesome, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at York, Pennsylvania, 3 February 1839. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.) to B. S. Ewell, at Prince Edward Court House, Virginia. Postmarked Millford Mills, Prince Edward County, Virginia, June 1840. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.) to Professor Benjamin S. Ewell, at Prince Edward Court House, Virginia. Postmarked Buckland, 28 May 1842. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.), at Stony Lonesome, Prince William County, Virginia, to B. S. Ewell, at Hampden Sidney College, Prince Edward Court House, Virginia, 15 December 1845. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.) to B. S. Ewell, at Hampden Sidney College, Prince Edward Court House, Virginia. Postmarked Buckland, Virginia, 31 January 1846. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.) to B. S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia, 16 May 1850. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.) to B. S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia. Postmarked Buckland, Virginia, 17 February 1851. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.), at Washington, D.C., to Benjamin S. Ewell, 14 November 1851. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.) to her mother, Elizabeth Ewell, August 1857., 2 items. (Folder 9)
      - Letter, 5 August 1857. (Folder 9)
      - Letter, 31 August 1857. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.) to Benjamin S. Ewell, at West Point, New York. Postmarked Fairfax Court House, no date. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.), at Brook Grove, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at York, Pennsylvania, no date. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Rebecca L.), at Stony Lonesome, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at York, Pennsylvania, no date. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Richard S.) to William Stoddert, no date. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Richard S.) to Benjamin S. Ewell. (Folder 9)
    - Ewell (Thomas), father of Benjamin S. Ewell, to his father, Col. Jesse Ewell, at Dumfries, Prince William County, Virginia, 20 December 1802. (Folder 10)
      Enclosure: Copy of an account of T. Ewell with his father.
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to his mother, Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia, December 1837-January 1838., 2 items. (Folder 10)
      - Letter, 3 December 1837. (Folder 10)
      - Letter, 18 January 1838. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Nashville, Tennessee, to his mother, Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia, 1 July 1838. (Folder 10)
      Harriot Campbell, at Nashville, Tennessee, to Betsy Ewell. 1 July 1838. (On same sheet.)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Nashville, Tennessee, to his mother, Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia, 1 September 1838. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Nashville, Tennessee, to his sister, Rebecca L. Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia, 6 October 1838. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Nashville, Tennessee, to his mother, Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia, 9 December 1838. (Folder 10)
      Lizinka Campbell to Rebecca Ewell. (On same sheet.)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Nashville, Tennessee, to Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia, 27 April 1839. (Folder 10)
      Harriot Campbell to her sister, Elizabeth Ewell. (On same sheet.)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Nashville, Tennessee, to his aunt, Mary Jane S. Stoddert, at Jackson, Tennessee, 27 April 1839. (Folder 10)
      Thomas Ewell to Harriet Stoddert. (On same sheet.)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Nashville, Tennessee, to his mother, Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia, 10 July 1839. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Nashville, Tennessee, to his brother, Benjamin S. Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia, 12 September 1839. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Nashville, Tennessee, to Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia, 25 September 1839. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia, January-February 1840., 2 items. (Folder 10)
      - Letter, 9 January 1840. (Folder 10)
      - Letter, 4 February 1840. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Millford Mills, Prince William County, Virginia, 7 March 1840. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to his aunt, Mary Jane S. Stoddert, at Greensborough, Greene County, Alabama, 13 September 1840. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Millford Mills, Prince William County, Virginia, 17 October 1840. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at Prince Edward Court House, Virginia, 22 October 1840. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas) to Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Millford Mills, Prince William County, Virginia, 7 March 1841. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), to B. S. Ewell, at Hampden Sidney College, Prince Edward Court House, Virginia, 4 April 1841. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to B. S. Ewell, at Prince Edward Court House, Virginia, 3 August 1841. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Millford Mills, Prince William County, Virginia, 7 September 1841. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to B. S. Ewell, at Prince Edward Court House, Virginia, 25 September 1841. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia, 3 November 1841. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to his sister, Elizabeth S. Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia, 30 December 1841. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to his mother, Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia, 27 February 1842. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to B. S. Ewell, at Prince Edward Court House, Virginia, 12 March 1842. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia, April-August 1842., 3 items. (Folder 10)
      - Letter, 30 April 1842. (Folder 10)
      - Letter, 17 June 1842. (Folder 10)
      - Letter, 17 August 1842. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at Hampden Sidney College, Prince Edward Court House, Virginia, 1 September 1842. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia, 27 November 1842. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to Rebecca L. Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia, 2 February 1843. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia, March-May 1843., 3 items. (Folder 10)
      - Letter, 2 March 1843. (Folder 10)
      - Letter, 14 March 1843. (Folder 10)
      - Letter, 8 May 1843. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Alum Springs, Rockbridge County, Virginia, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at Hampden Sidney College, Prince Edward Court House, Virginia, 6 September 1845. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to B. S. Ewell, at Hampden Sidney College, Prince Edward Court House, Virginia, November 1845-January 1846., 2 items. (Folder 10)
      - Letter, 17 November 1845. (Folder 10)
      - Letter, 1 January 1846. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at St. Louis, to Benjamin S. Ewell, 6 December 1846. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia, undated., Four undated letters. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (Thomas), at Jackson, Tennessee, to his sister, Elizabeth S. Ewell, at Greenwich, Prince William County, Virginia. (Folder 10)
    - Ewell (William), at George Town, to Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell, at Hay Market, Prince William County, Virginia, 4 November 1824. (Folder 10)
  - Letters: F-G, 1784-1934 (Folder 11)
    - Flourney (Mrs. R. W.). (Folder 11)
      Invitation to a tea.
    - Forest (Douglas F.), at St. John's Rectory, near Ellicott City, Maryland, to B. S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia, 21 July 1875. (Folder 11)
    - Forest (Douglas F.), at Washington, D.C., to the President and Faculty of William and Mary College, 26 March 1879. (Folder 11)
    - Fry (E. F.), at Lynnville, Tennessee, to Elizabeth S. Ewell, sister of Benjamin S. Ewell, at Georgetown, 27 January 1887. (Folder 11)
    - Fulton (William), at Salisbury, Maryland, to Benjamin S. Ewell, 29 July 1872. (Folder 11)
    - Gache (L. H.), at Baltimore, to Elizabeth S. Ewell, sister of Benjamin S. Ewell, 29 August 1867. (Folder 11)
    - Gache (L. H.), at Philadelphia, to Miss L. Ewell, [i.e., Elizabeth S. Ewell, sister of Benjamin S. Ewell], 18 June 1899. (Folder 11)
    - Gache (L. H.), at Philadelphia, to Elizabeth Ewell Scott, September 1899-February 1901., 2 items. (Folder 11)
      - Letter, 29 September 1899. (Folder 11)
      - Letter, 15 February 1901. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Ann), at Brookgrove, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at West Point, New York Postmarked Bladensburgh, Maryland, 10 January 1831. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Ann) to Benjamin S. Ewell, at West Point, New York. Postmarked Bladensburgh, Maryland, 23 October 1831. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Ann), at St. Louis, to Benjamin S. Ewell, 22 December 1849. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Ann), at Washington, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia, 4 October 1850. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at Brook Grove, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at West Point, New York. Postmarked Bladensburgh, Maryland. Mrs. Elizabeth Ewell to her son, Benjamin S. Ewell. (On same sheet.) A. Gantt to Benjamin S. Ewell. (On same sheet.), 31 May 1831. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at West Point, New York, to Rebecca L. Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia, December 1831- June 1832., 2 items. (Folder 11)
      - Letter, 17 December 1831. (Folder 11)
      - Letter, 10 June 1832. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.) to Benjamin S. Ewell, at West Point, New York Postmarked Bladensburg, Maryland, February-June 1835., 3 items. (Folder 11)
      - Letter, 11 February 1835. (Folder 11)
      - Letter, 4 April 1835. (Folder 11)
      - Letter, 2 June 1835. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.) to Benjamin S. Ewell, at York, Pennsylvania. Postmarked Bladensburg, Maryland, 23 September 1836. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at Upper Marlboro, Maryland, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at York, Pennsylvania, 21 May 1838. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at Brook Grove, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at York, Pennsylvania. Postmarked Bladensburg, Maryland, 30 December 1838. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at Brook Grove, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia. Postmarked Bladensburg, Maryland, 29 April 1839. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at St. Louis, Missouri, to Rebecca L. Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia, 29 September 1839. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at St. Louis, to Rebecca L. Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia, 31 January 1840. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at St. Louis, Missouri, to Rebecca L. Ewell, at Millford Mills P.O., Prince William County, Virginia, 12 May 1841. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at St. Louis, Missouri, to Benjamin S. Ewell, 8 March 1850. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at St. Louis, Missouri, to B. S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia, 15 September 1853. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.) to Lizinka [ ? ], 18 April 1865. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at St. Louis, Missouri, to Lizinka [ ? ], 21 April 1865. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at St. Louis, Missouri, to Rebecca L. Ewell, at Baltimore, Maryland, 4 June 1865. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at St. Louis, Missouri, to Rebecca Ewell, 9 September 1865. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at St. Louis, Missouri, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at Buckland, Prince William County, Virginia. Forwarded to Lexington, Rockbridge County, Virginia, 16 August 1868. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at St. Louis, to B. S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia, 27 May 1878. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at St. Louis, to Elizabeth S. Ewell, sister of Benjamin S. Ewell, at Georgetown, D.C., 7 June 1876. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at St. Louis, to Elizabeth S. Ewell, at Georgetown, D.C., 4 February 1884. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at St. Louis, to Col. B. S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia, 26 July 1886. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (Thomas T.), at St. Louis, to Col. B. S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia, 28 January 1888. (Folder 11)
    - Gantt (M. C.) to Rebecca Ewell, at Bristoe [i.e., Bristow] Station, Prince William County, Virginia Postmarked Georgetown D.C. (Folder 11)
    - Garrett (R. S.), Adjutant General, at Head Quarters Virginia Forces, Richmond, Virginia, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia, 27 April 1861. (Folder 11)
    - Gilman (D. C.), at Baltimore, Maryland, to President Benjamin S. Ewell.(In William and Mary Papers.), 28 May 1887. (Folder 11)
    - Gilmore (James H.), at the University of Virginia, to Col. Benjamin S. Ewell, at Ewell P.O., James City County, Virginia, 30 May 1893. (Folder 11)
    - Goode (John), at Washington, D.C., to Col. B. S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia, 21 February 1880. (Folder 11)
    - Gordan (S. L.), at Charlottesville, Virginia, to Col. Benjamin S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia, 24 November 1887. (Folder 11)
    - Grant (U. S.), at New York, to Elizabeth S. Ewell, sister of Benjamin S. Ewell, at Georgetown, D.C., 3 February 1882. (Folder 11)
    - Greenleaf (Mary L.), at Hillside, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at Prince Edward Court House, Virginia. Postmarked Charlotte Court House, Virginia, 2 January 1845. (Folder 11)
    - Griffin (J. L. C.), at Sharon, Mississippi, to President Benjamin S. Ewell. (In William and Mary Papers.), 12 January 1855. (Folder 11)
    - Grisby (Hugh Blair), at Charlotte Court House, Virginia, to Benjamin S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia. (In William and Mary Papers.), 2 January 1868. (Folder 11)
    - Grisby (Hugh Blair), at Edgehill, to Col. Benjamin S. Ewell, at Williamsburg, Virginia (In William and Mary Papers.), 2 June 1872. (Folder 11)